<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<enchants>
	<boostedlevel>
		%s is the best you have been able to achieve thus far, but you want more. With the power of liquid chroma, %s is within your reach.
	</boostedlevel>
	<weaponaoe>
		Your sword of an unbreakable alloy of metal and the world's very foundation is wonderful, but even it is somewhat outmatched should you find yourself in the midst of a crowd. With some luck, that will no longer be an obstacle.
	</weaponaoe>
	<aggromask>
		Unsurprisingly, one of the fastest ways to anger any creature in the world is to attack them. It makes sense, but what if you could somehow deal that damage without them being any the wiser? Even better, you would be able to kill the nether pigmen without being swarmed by ten of them.
	</aggromask>
	<enderlock>
		Ranged weapons like bows are extremely convenient, letting you kill a mob at a safe distance, but they have long been unable to deal any damage to Endermen, who just mockingly teleport away. Time to put an end to that.
	</enderlock>
	<userepair>
		You put your heart, soul, half your platinum and who knows how much experience into the ultimate weapon, but the damn thing has a durability of 200 uses and you almost want to never use it. Perhaps if you could leech some of the health off the mobs you kill to heal your weapon.
	</userepair>
	<rareloot>
		Looting III helps, sure, but it seems to do little for some particularly uncommon drops, including heads, equipment, and the occasional metal ingot. This may not help improve your yields of gunpowder, string, or blaze rods, but it will help with the rarer ones.
	</rareloot>
	<fastsink>
		You wish to build a base out of the dark stone that forms geodes across the ocean floor, but having to dive for it from the surface - and expend half your air just on the way down - severely hampers its acquisition. You would not have thought one would want to sink like a rock, but apparently you now do.
	</fastsink>
	<harvestlevel>
		Wood mines stone. Stone mines iron. Iron mines diamond. Diamond mines obsidian. This progression is indelibly set into nearly everyone's mind. Now you get to break it.
	</harvestlevel>
	<airminer>
		Though you long ago achieved the ability to fly - either by strapping rockets to your back or via more magical means - the fact that your ability to mine blocks is greatly impeded while in flight is an endless annoyance. Stabilizing your tool should help fix that.
	</airminer>
	<phasing>
		Combat becomes somewhat pointless when both you and your opponent have nigh-impenetrable armor or magic energy shields upon which you can unload every weapon you have and never make a scratch. You may not have the means to disable said protection outright (nor would that go over well with those relying on such protection), but if you could focus a portion of your damage so it can punch through...
	</phasing>
	<autocollect>
		More than once you have delighted in a rare find deep in a cave, then upon mining the valuable ore, finding out too late that it was directly adjacent to lava and watching helplessly as the items are incinerated. Carefully digging out the surroundings first is an unacceptable amount of work - you want something that will instead make the contents of the blocks you mine automatically enter your inventory.
	</autocollect>
	<bosskill>
		Over the course of your exploits, you have run across a small handful of creatures - often found deep in mysterious structures or guarding over some alien realm - that are an enormous hassle to kill as they seem to be able to soak up inordinate amounts of damage. You might be able to specialize a tool to take these creatures down, at the cost of utility on more ordinary creatures.
	</bosskill>
	<minetime>
		The efficiency enchantment is useful for mining obsidian and the green stone from which some sadist carved a maze, but in accelerating the mining of those materials, your tool is now unusuably powerful for more mundane terrain. Indeed, a simple tap on a wall of limestone, netherrack, or sandstone and you have a hole that looks like you tried decorating with live TNT. With some refinement, that effect can be mitigated.
	</minetime>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
</enchants>
