<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<hover>
	<crystals>
		Concentrated crystal energy; seems to radiate weak effects related with the associated element. Fragile and not easily moved.
	</crystals>
	<pylon>
		A powerful emitter of crystal energy. You are likely to need these later on.
	</pylon>
	<rune>
		Runes seem to be able to act as weak foci for crystal energy of their color.
	</rune>
	<ore_infused>
		Seams of energy run through this rock; its contents are likely useful in your endeavours.
	</ore_infused>
	<ore_stones>
		Embedded in the stone appears to be a different kind of rock, one which glows with energy.
	</ore_stones>
	<ore_binding>
		Fossilized crystals, fused together. Their color long since gone, they no longer contain energy but may be a good substrate.
	</ore_binding>
	<ore_focal>
		Glowing an angry red, this rock may well have the capability to act as a lens for crystal energy.
	</ore_focal>
	<ore_teleport>
		The similarity between the color of these gems and the color of an ender pearl is probably no coincidence.
	</ore_teleport>
	<ore_watery>
		Watery in both color and texture, the powder from this rock is probably imbued with the essence of fluidity.
	</ore_watery>
	<ore_firaxite>
		Palpably warm, Firaxite must be associated with heat energy.
	</ore_firaxite>
	<ore_luma>
		Glowing brightly, the contents of this stone no doubt enhance the power of lumen transmission.
	</ore_luma>
	<ore_echo>
		Vibrations pass back and forth through this rock; harnessing them might become a priority.
	</ore_echo>
	<ore_firestone>
		Buried deep in the nether, it is no surprise the gems in this rock are almost painfully hot.
	</ore_firestone>
	<ore_thermite>
		This rock is barely able to contain the energy within. Maybe if released it could act as a powerful emitter.
	</ore_thermite>
	<ore_reso>
		These pulsing crystals might hold the secret to warping space itself.
	</ore_reso>
	<ore_spacerift>
		This material might provide a key to being able to relocate oneself at will.
	</ore_spacerift>
	<ore_rainbow>
		Refractory gems are embedded in this stone. Maybe they can be used to help focus the energy from pylons.
	</ore_rainbow>
	<ore_avolite>
		These crystals glow with energy. They can probably act as a reservoir for it.
	</ore_avolite>
	<plant_flower>
		This gently glowing flower seems to weakly radiate energy; if extracted, its contents likely are crucial in maintaining an aura.
	</plant_flower>
	<plant_cave>
		Sparkling in the dark, there is something cleansing about the essence of this plant.
	</plant_cave>
	<plant_lily>
		This lily throbs will all colors of energy; perhaps its extracts could be used as a sort of unifier.
	</plant_lily>
	<plant_bulb>
		Hanging from the underside of leaves, these bulbs are filled with a magical dust of unknown nature.
	</plant_bulb>
	<plant_desert>
		This bush gives off a powerful aura - no doubt it will be critical in constructing beacons of your own.
	</plant_desert>
	<plant_pod>
		This pod is full of gently glowing beans. Likely not a foodstuff, it may well have other uses.
	</plant_pod>
	<plant_root>
		This root strengthens and enriches the tree on which it grows. Perhaps you can put it to a similar use.
	</plant_root>
	<rainbowleaf>
		Never before have you seen a tree like this. With leaves of every color of the rainbow, there must be more to this tree than meets the eye.
	</rainbowleaf>
	<flower_enderflower>
		The growth pattern of these flowers - literally jumping from location to location - is no doubt a hint to their utility.
	</flower_enderflower>
	<flower_lumalily>
		It can surely be no coincidence that these flowers, found in the frozen climates, are icy and bind things together.
	</flower_lumalily>
	<flower_resoclover>
		The energetic sparks surrounding this plant offer a clue as to the usefulness of their internals.
	</flower_resoclover>
	<flower_sanobloom>
		High atop the jungle canopy, these berries might be useful in combination with another form of berry...
	</flower_sanobloom>
	<flower_voidreed>
		Looking into the gentle aura given off by these reeds gives you a sense of vertigo and space.
	</flower_voidreed>
	<flower_flowivy>
		Growing like a weed, this fast-spreading ivy is almost nature incarnate.
	</flower_flowivy>
	<flower_glowdaisy>
		Lighting the floor underneath the cliffs, these glowing flowers sparkle, and may serve as more than mere decoration.
	</flower_glowdaisy>
	<flower_glowroot>
		Hanging down from the rock above, these vines both light the darkness and occasionally drop seeds which have...interesting effects on nearby plant life.
	</flower_glowroot>
	<dyeleaf>
		Brightly hued leaves cover this tree, and it appears that berries sprout from the twigs.
	</dyeleaf>
	<dyeflower>
	
	</dyeflower>
	<dimensioncore>
		Vibrantly hued and energetically luminous, this...thing is of obvious value.
	</dimensioncore>
	<hive>
		A beehive. Underground. In that case, the bees inside are probably somewhat unusual, and perhaps even valuable. One would expect that a fabric cup would not exactly suffice for obtaining it.
	</hive>
	<dimbedrock>
		Digging down normally brings feelings of dread, but in this world you feel peace; What else might be different about the bottom of this world?
	</dimbedrock>
	<mud>
		Residual traces of liquid, weakly radiating the magic energy it contains. Unfortunately, it is thoroughly contaminated by the large amounts of random debris it has absorbed from the local foliage and cannot be harvested or used.
	</mud>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
</hover>
