<?xml version="1.0"?>
<hover>
	<crystals>
		Concentrated crystal energy; seems to radiate weak effects related with the associated element. Fragile and not easily moved.
	</crystals>
	<pylon>
		A powerful emitter of crystal energy. You are likely to need these later on.
	</pylon>
	<rune>
		Runes seem to be able to act as weak foci for crystal energy of their color.
	</rune>
	<ore0>
		Seams of energy run through this rock; its contents are likely useful in your endeavours.
	</ore0>
	<ore1>
		Embedded in the stone appears to be a different kind of rock, one which glows with energy.
	</ore1>
	<ore2>
		Fossilized crystals, fused together. Their color long since gone, they no longer contain energy but may be a good substrate.
	</ore2>
	<ore3>
		Glowing an angry red, this rock may well have the capability to act as a lens for crystal energy.
	</ore3>
	<ore4>
		The similarity between the color of these gems and the color of an ender pearl is probably no coincidence.
	</ore4>
	<ore5>
		Watery in both color and texture, the powder from this rock is probably imbued with the essence of fluidity.
	</ore5>
	<ore6>
		Palpably warm, Firaxite must be associated with heat energy.
	</ore6>
	<ore7>
		
	</ore7>
	<ore8>
		
	</ore8>
	<ore9>
		Buried deep in the nether, it is no surprise the gems in this rock are almost painfully hot.
	</ore9>
	<ore10>
		This rock is barely able to contain the energy within. Maybe if released it could act as a powerful emitter.
	</ore10>
	<ore11>
		These pulsing crystals might hold the secret to warping space itself.
	</ore11>
	<ore12>
		This material might provide a key to being able to relocate oneself at will.
	</ore12>
	<plant0>
		This gently glowing flower seems to weakly radiate energy; if extracted, its contents likely are crucial in maintaining an aura.
	</plant0>
	<plant1>
		Sparkling in the dark, there is something cleansing about the essence of this plant.
	</plant1>
	<plant2>
		This lily throbs will all colors of energy; perhaps its extracts could be used as a sort of unifier.
	</plant2>
	<plant3>
		Hanging from the underside of leaves, these bulbs are filled with a magical dust of unknown nature.
	</plant3>
	<plant4>
		This bush gives off a powerful aura - no doubt it will be critical in constructing beacons of your own.
	</plant4>
	<rainbowleaf>
		Never before have you seen a tree like this. With leaves of every color of the rainbow, there must be more to this tree than meets the eye.
	</rainbowleaf>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
	<name>
	
	</name>
</hover>