<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info>
	<elements>
		You quickly realized that the magic elements that shape and drive the world are divided into sixteen types, each with an associated color.
	</elements>
	<crystals>
		Crystal energy, if it reaches a critical density, seems to coalesce and crystallize, forming interesting structures that radiate an aura related to the crystal. Aside from their obvious utility as a source of mild effect boosts, their stored crystal energy is clearly going to be invaluable. One wonders how they handle the corrupting influence of the Nether...
	</crystals>
	<pylons>
		At points where the energy field seems to be the strongest, you tend to find dark stone structures adorned with sparkling aura and topped with a beacon that visibly and audibly radiates raw power. Unfiltered and uncontained, they seem too powerful and unstable - a lesson you quickly learned - to be easily used, but you suspect that later on they will be a key component of your research.
	</pylons>
	<transmission>
		Pylons are the power sources, radiating crystal energy of their color. It stands to reason that you will have or make receivers requiring that energy. How, though, are you to transport that energy over the long distances between the pylons and where it is needed?
	</transmission>
	<start>
		This world is stange, confusing, and unknown. You have no idea what drives or forms it, something you will need to learn before you can possibly begin to exploit it and bend the forces to your needs. Fortunately for you, you have a notebook of sorts, though you will need to populate it with information you collect as you explore and experiment.
	</start>
	<crafting>
		At first, the casting table seemed identical to a wooden worktable, but you soon realized that in that form it can only make the most basic of items. In all likelihood, you will need to build a structure around the table to help focus the energy and allow you to advance your crafting. Additionally, the directionality to the recipes is likely important; one can only hope that the logical mapping of upwards to North has been chosen.
	</crafting>
	<balllightning>
		Pylons and rainbow forests seem to have interesting phenomena flitting about, wandering through the sky and around the ground. You wonder if they have a use, or if they might be dangerous. Even if not dangerous directly, you probably want to avoid letting them into sensitive machinery like a turbine.
	</balllightning>
	<apirecipes>
		Recalling the constructs you have crafted for other purposes - often those bearing little resemblance to the rest of your designs, feeling more akin to part of some other whole - you notice that you can nonetheless manufacture them on your casting table as well.
	</apirecipes>
	<leylines>
		Pylons transmit energy in concentrated beams, which you have come to call ley lines (no relation to the similarly named phenomena those with poor reasoning skills attribute to extraterrestrial construction projects and spontaneous combustion of people). These beams have a maximum range, and additionally are blocked by anything even remotely opaque.
	</leylines>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
</info>