<?xml version="1.0"?>
<machines>
	<accelerator>
		<desc>
			As you have already learned, light blue energy is associated most with time and its manipulation. By concentrating this energy and binding it in a crystal structure - a vast improvement over the previous design you scribbled out after slipping and knocking yourself unconscious on a cauldron - you might be able to set up a localized field in which time progresses at a greatly increased rate.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Comes in various tiers, each tier being twice as powerful as the last
			Localized effects may be ineffective over things whose essence is less concentrated
		</note>
	</accelerator>
	<guardian>
		<desc>
			Too often you come home to find your constructions damaged or half of your valuables missing because someone snooping around your property helped themselves to your supplies. Sometimes you are fortunate and have those in power apply magical protection spells over your territory, but they are often of fairly limited range, and the less scrupulous will demand a steep payment from you to do so. Finally, however, you can protect yourself by applying a version of that yourself; each stone emits an aura that prevents those you do not trust from helping themselves to your resources or your structures.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Protects against block placement and breaking, and the opening of GUIs within a %d block range

			Owners and admins always have permissions
			The owner can also use /guardstone add/remove &#60;player&#62; to allow/deny others access <!-- The &# tags are for angle brackets. Do not touch those. -->
		</note>
	</guardian>
	<stand>
		<desc>
			In order to achieve your more grandoise casting arrangements, you will need to expand the grid beyond a 3x3, and that means you need a receptacle on which to store the items. Integrated into the structures around your table, these stands serve exactly that purpose, allowing you a 5x5 grid. The outer ring will need to be elevated by a block so that they have a clear line of sight to the table.
		</desc>
		<note>
			
		</note>
	</stand>
	<telepump>
		<desc>
			You already have all sorts of automated pumps and devices to drain large pools of liquid. However, some liquids, irritatingly, occur not in large lakes or wells but in scattered ponds all over the place and thus force you to either bucket it manually or spend more time moving the pump and pipes than actually pumping. The teleportation pump, by using movement energy, solves this problem by draining a large area of disconnected lakes at once, greatly expediting fluid acquisition.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Needs to scan the area after being placed
			Base Cost per block:
			%s
		</note>
	</telepump>
	<miner>
		<desc>
			Most of your time mining is wasted digging out mountains of rock to find scattered blocks of ore or other valuables, making the whole process a tedious chore that is done more out of necessity than any sort of enjoyment. Even most automated methods of acquiring resources have this problem, wasting a large amount of time and energy, leaving you with nothing to show for it except 50 chests of cobblestone. The mineral extractor, however, is able to sense the presence of value in the world, allowing it to pinpoint the locations of ores and other valuables.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Needs to scan the area after being placed, and can be triggered with the manipulator
			Base Cost per block:
			%s
		</note>
	</miner>
	<reprogrammer>
		<desc>
			Some madman has scattered dark metal cages throughout the world, in cobblestone rooms underground to old mining tunnels to red brick bridges in the Nether. These cages pump forth endless mobs, making them not only a dangerous hazard but a very useful device for farming the creature's drops. Unfortunately, while many have tried to replicate these structures, all have either failed or yielded a pale imitation of the original, and few designs allow you to customize the type of mob in the cage; after all, you can only use so much rotten flesh and spider eyes. This device will finally change that.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reprogrammer>
	<repeater>
		<desc>
			Your initial foray into transmitting lumen energy was a disaster. The basic wooden repeaters you created only marginally served their purpose, and were prone to often violent failure as they were used. In hindsight, wood was a monumentally foolish material to choose. Clearly the crystal you have used so much of would be a better choice. A rune to focus the color would improve them even better, though that would mean restricting it to only one color of transmission. You may find a way around that too...later.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: %d blocks receiving and transmitting
		</note>
	</repeater>
	<weakrepeater>
		<desc>
			The transmission range of a Crystal Pylon is limited to %d blocks, and its beams are blocked by just about anything aside from air and glass; this means that unless you built your base next to one of every pylon - a dangerous endeavour - you need some way to relay the signal. This is exactly the function of a repeater, which can repeat a signal and do so around obstacles. However, repeaters do incur a small signal attenuation, so optimizing the path is a good idea. This is only a first attempt at such repeaters, and as a result its quality is...questionable. Surely you will need to improve your designs with experience.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: %d blocks receiving and transmitting
		</note>
	</weakrepeater>
	<rift>
		<desc>
			Transporting things long-distance or between dimensions is one of the most annoying tasks you have to face; whether you built a structure in another world because of fear of a destructive failure or you are trying to transport a fluid from a source thousands of blocks away to your base, you often find yourself stymied by an inability to bridge the gap. Now, however, you can tie two disparate locations in the world together - no matter the distance or differences in dimension - and transport items, fluids, redstone, power of all kinds, and more through a link to the void.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Always placed in pairs

			What goes in one side of one rift comes out the opposite side of the other

			Item transport is directional, and a side must be chosen with the manipulator
		</note>
	</rift>
	<tank>
		<desc>
			Items are easy to store en masse - particularly after you found a way to store them in patterns on some strange purple crystals - but too often you find yourself out of storage for fluids that you collect or produce. Tanks of all sizes are already available to you, but even the largest ones, these mysterious metal boxes that only seem structurally stable in a few preset sizes, hold a few tens of thousands of buckets. By trapping a link to the void hole inside a glass frame and adding large quantities of fluid energy, you have a multiblock tank that can quickly reach enormous capacities.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Capacity is approximately %d*n^2 buckets, where n is the number of blocks in the tank

			Can be built to any size and shape, up to a capacity of %d buckets
		</note>
	</tank>
	<compound>
		<desc>
			Repeaters are all well and good, but they suffer two problems. One, if you have a number of pylons all along the same path, laying multiple tracks of repeaters is messy and costly. Two, if your base is not easily accessed from the outside, you are forced to punch one hole for each color channel. The multi-aura repeater solves both of these; though larger and much more costly, they can carry all sixteen colors - including simultaneously. They do, however, have a larger per-node attenuation, meaning you will want to keep their use to a minimum.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</compound>
	<charger>
		<desc>
			You have already figured out how to make a crystal that can selectively take in and release crystal energy, but you are in need of a way to funnel that energy - which unfiltered would probably violently overload the crystal - safely and efficiently. Recalling something about sharp corners concentrating stress in materials - the details escape you due to the lack of attention you paid at the time (a decision you now regret) - you try to do the same for the crystal, building a frame to shield the edges and focus the energy into the center. As to why it spins...what you don't know can't hurt you, right?
		</desc>
		<note>
			Stores up to %d lumens of each color
		</note>
	</charger>
	<heatlily>
		<desc>
			You, in your (less than) infinite wisdom, decided to make a sugarcane farm in a snow biome. It worked perfectly...until the water froze and your sugarcane rotted on the ground. You need some way to heat the water and stave off the cold in a small area around the farm. Maybe if you used some essence of those mechanical-sounding fire creatures from the Nether bridges, you could make a plant that not only served that purpose, but was aesthetically pleasing as well. This should also help prevent your high-drop landing pools from freezing over. (Ow.)
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</heatlily>
	<ticker>
		<desc>
			You spent quite a lot of effort making the perfect set of tools; some are made of a blend of different materials, including some exotic alloys (a hard purple one seems particularly useful). Fortunately for you, you can put moss all over the tool and this (somehow) makes it regenerate its durability. The only problem is, the moss seems to be triggered by your body heat, so sticking the tools in a chest to let them repair does you little good. If you could somehow concentrate life energy, along with some amount of time, you may be able to construct something to achieve the same effect, and possibly faster as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires:
			%s
		</note>
	</ticker>
	<fence>
		<desc>
			You need some way of protecting your base from the hordes of mobs outside, and fences are rather boring. You already tried using moats (how does a spider the size of a cow swim!?) to no effect, and you tried using unshielding wires as an impromptu electric fence, an experiment that ended after you had the misfortune of touching it yourself. However, with (a large amount of) energy associated with protection and shielding, you can make a barrier that will stop creatures of all types while letting you pass unharmed, and can be built into any shape between connected nodes.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a perimeter with vertices marked by either fence emitters or relays. Right click with manipulator to calculate perimeter, shift-right-click to set output side
			
			Each emitter in the perimeter adds to the damage dealt to intruding entities
		</note>
	</fence>
	<furnace>
		<desc>
			Smelting. One of the most boring, mundane tasks you nonetheless still find yourself forced to do. Sure, there are all sorts of ways to speed up the process - although the external heating methods have a nastly tendency of liquefying the whole setup - but you might now be able to enhance the yield with a new kind of furnace able to harness not only fire but also enhancement energy as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Yields %dx output for anything smelted inside it except for ingot dusts
		</note>
	</furnace>
	<laser>
		<desc>
			Standard light can be focused into a beam, so it stands to reason that you can do the same with lumen energy with the appropriate lens. That is exactly the function of this device. With it, you can focus energy of any color in a thin beam along a line of blocks - up to %d blocks away - thus applying the effects of that color. Now if only you had any idea what each color did...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</laser>
	<itemrift>
		<desc>
			A classic transport problem involves two inventories within a clear line of sight to each other but separated by several blocks. You once saw a device you can attach to each block and rapidly transport the contents, but it was limited to a single block of space; this, however, is a longer-ranged variant.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</itemrift>
	<crystal>
		<desc>
			Once you started to do a lot of pylon-driven crafting, or started to charge yourself with large quantities of crystal energy, you made a crucial observation: Pylons are not infinite, but lose their color as they are drained. Granted, they do recharge, but slowly - though planting similarly colored trees around them helps a bit. However, you have found that these crystals, being raw elemental energy cast into crystal form, can dramatically increase the charging speed of a pylon, with a full, balanced ring of eight speeding it up enormously.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</crystal>
	<infuser>
		<desc>
			Tossing raw shards into pools of chroma is one thing, but the purified shards you made do not seem to respond to such a crude attempt at infusion. A better strategy would be to build a dedicated receptacle for the items, and surround it with a moat of chroma, thus setting up a vortex to funnel the energy into the items.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</infuser>
	<fabricator>
		<desc>
			You have already seen how many items contain trace amounts of various crystal elements, leading you to wonder if the reverse is also true. After much experimentation, you devise an odd contraption that collects crystal energy on large paddles, and funnels it to the center, where it can be formed into an item. You do of course require one item first, as a sort of blueprint, and you note that only some more simplistic items can be fabricated.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires %d*(%.1f*n^%d) lumens per unit naturally present on the item
		</note>
	</fabricator>
	<beacon>
		<desc>
			After an unfortunate encounter with an engine intake, you have been desperately seeking a way to protect yourself from the more hazardous situations you always seem to end up in. Recalling the enormous protective power of %s crystal energy to protect, you try building a beacon that radiates the energy into the air. As long as it stays supplied with energy - not an easy task, given the large energy expenditure - you may well be impossible to kill.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Uses %dn^%d lumens per half-heart of damage
			Max range %d blocks
		</note>
	</beacon>
	<enchanter>
		<desc>
			Enchanting has always been a random and infurating process. Spend a week collecting experience and you might get Bane of Arthropods I, or you might be lucky enough to get Fortune III and Efficiency V off of a few levels. Rather than tear your hair out trying to spend your experience efficiently, you recall the liquid chroma, which, being concentrated experience, may allow you not only automatic enchanting, but to allow you more fine control over the actual enchantments as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Each level of enchantment requires %d mB of Chroma
		</note>
	</enchanter>
	<chromaflower>
		<desc>
			You may not be that guy that builds 9x9 cobblestone boxes for a house, but nonetheless your ability to make your territory visually appealing has rested more on access to fancy decorations than raw architectural design. With that in mind, you work on enhancing a lowly flower with crystal energy. The end result is certainly interesting, with its gently pulsing colors, but it may also have a functional use as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</chromaflower>
	<collector>
		<desc>
			Being able to convert and concentrate experience into chroma is one thing, but until now you have been at a loss as to how to actually do that. Fortunately for you, you stumbed upon the answer while fiddling with some crystal shards; running experience over them, either draining off yourself or pumped in in liquid form, seems to catalyze the reaction.
		</desc>
		<note>
			%d XP = 1 mB of Chroma
		</note>
	</collector>
	<brewer>
		<desc>
			Everyone loves making potions...OK, no. Between collecting a hideous red weed that seems to grow so slowly you could mine a chunk before it grew, to fiddling with arcane procedures that seem designed as a last-resort replacement for something even worse, to burning through valuable ingredients for effects that last mere minutes - and at the expense of a boosted effect too! - nobody sane enjoys this process. At the very least, maybe, you can forgo most of the process by using the energy from the crystal shards instead, making the process actually worth your time.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Standard shards yield Level I 3:00 potions
			Boosted shards yield Level II 8:00 potions
		</note>
	</brewer>
	<ritual>
		<desc>
			You have heard mention of all these special abilities you can gain by imbuing yourself with large quantities of crystal energy, but you need some means to carry out the infusion. After an incident that shall never be mentioned again - and if anyone asks, no, you do not have anything to do with the crater where that village used to be - you recall the shards' infusion process. If it worked for items, maybe it will work for you as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</ritual>
	<table>
		<desc>
			Wooden crafting tables, useful as they are, have their limitations. To that end, you have found a way to affix crystal plating to a table, allowing it to store and process crystal energy, this allowing you to craft items that require magical interaction. Hopefully this one will turn out better than your other design, given that this one is not asking you to surround it with skulls or face the consequences of lightning, explosions, and noxious purple gas. You are initially unfamiliar with the table, precluding advanced use, but as you grow accustomed to it, you can be more adventurous.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</table>
	<itemcollector>
		<desc>
			Despite your best attempts, you have not been able to totally avert the need for farming, and your mountain of grey seeds and beige goo can attest to that. Unfortunately, farms tend to scatter items far and wide, leading to the need for either powerful item collection systems - which have their own problems - or a problem with so many items on the ground you find it hard to move. The item collector at last is an answer to this problem, being able to collect items anywhere in its range as soon as they are created.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: +/- %d blocks horizontally, +/- %d blocks vertically
		</note>
	</itemcollector>
	<aishutdown>
		<desc>
			Animal farms are an eternal headache. Between cows' endless noise and chickens' tendency to get out of any enclosure you try to keep them in, you would gleefully exterminate every one of them if not for the fact that you need a supply of leather, feathers, wool, and meat. If there was some way to stun them, to freeze their thought processes, this would probably help a great deal.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aishutdown>
	<aspect>
		<desc>
			Aside from their use as impromptu musical instruments, those jars of colored liquids you get when melting down random items have an actual use; When you decided to pursue another branch of magic, you found yourself in need of endless numbers of them. The problem is, the process of melting items into raw essentia is slow and hard to automate. With your knowledge of crystal energy, however, you have finally made a device capable of collecting crystal energy and converting it into essentia, though not exactly cheaply.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aspect>
	<lamp>
		<desc>
			The standard method of keeping unwanted creatures away is to light the area, but that is often difficult or ugly to do, and the best designs can be rendered worthless with one block left a bit too dark. With that in mind, you seek to concentrate crystal energy, being luminous itself, in some sort of lamp to keep the mobs at bay.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: %d for each element in the lamp
		</note>
	</lamp>
	<powertree>
		<desc>
			Even with power crystals in place, pylons still remain incapable of handling very heavy load. That, combined with the tedium of venturing to them every time you need to recharge yourself, leads you to dream of a way to store energy in larger quantities, effectively a battery. Obviously a simple box would not be the correct approach, but maybe if you built some sort of structure, it could grow organically. As long as the energy remains pure...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Capacity: %d+%dn^%d, where n is the number of leaf blocks
			Cannot function without a view of the sky
		</note>
	</powertree>
	<lampcontrol>
		<desc>
			You often find yourself in need of controllable lighting, but redstone, even when you figured out how to alloy it into iron and stick it on the ceiling, is clumsy and requires false floors and ceiling in order to hide unslightly wiring. However, the magic aura, which you can control, may allow you to manipulate many separate lamps at a distance, obviating that need.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Max Range: %d
			Max Channel: %d
			Can be controlled manually, with redstone, by the charge state of an RF battery, or with shaft power
		</note>
	</lampcontrol>
	<aspectjar>
		<desc>
			This fabrication process gives you nightmares. Not only is it incredibly unstable - more than once the thing has exploded, sent items flying, or done other nasty things - and to top it off it draws liquid essence out of jars that must be placed around the construct. This would be fine, were it not for the small capacity of these jars, meaning filling them - another tedious process - is a constant necessity. Being able to store more essentia in a jar - perhaps even multiple types! - would be of enormous convenience.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Primal Aspect Capacity: %d
			Other Aspect Capacity: %d
		</note>
	</aspectjar>
	<farmer>
		<desc>
			Harvesting crops is somewhat of a hassle. Doing it manually is extremely slow and ineffective, and those fans you used, while they work, are loud and tend to send items flying. Channelling nature-based energy is likely to provide a superior solution.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</farmer>
	<automator>
		<desc>
			Though less of a hassle than some other fabrication systems - that pyramidal altar nearly left you dead on the table - it can still be tedious, particularly with recursive crafting that can take quite a bit of time. This is where an idea hits you - you should be familiar enough with some of these recipes that you might be able to set up some sort of system to automatically perform them, reducing the amount of work by an enormous amount.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</automator>
	<biomepainter>
		<desc>
			Too often you find yourself in need of tweaking the climate around you, often because some task you are working on requires specific temperatures or humidities (those bees you were working on proved particularly inflexible). It is not too much of a stretch to imagine that you might be able to use crystal energy to accomplish that task, and on top of that make it as easy as painting on a canvas.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</biomepainter>
	<medistributor>
		<desc>
			That digitial storage system of yours is unmatched in its convenience, except for one thing. Though it has a special device for pumping out items, and another for using internal item buffers to control a redstone signal, doing this with multiple items quickly becomes infeasible. To that end, you have designed an assembly that can function as several of these in parallel, allowing you to always maintain certain item levels in the system.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</medistributor>
	<rfdistributor>
		<desc>
			You thought that it could hardly get any easier with this kind of power; simply hook up the conduits from a generator to a machine and everything worked. However, you were still presented with one final dilemma: When grouping machines together, the cluster of cables is both unsightly and inconvenient to navigate around. Some way to transmit that power wirelessly from above would solve this problem.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</rfdistributor>
	<window>
		<desc>
			Some say a special kind of window exists, one that should you gaze into it, might just find that the view on the other side becomes your reality.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a square frame of crystal-based stone, such as crystalline stone, shielding stone, or obsidian, and to be linked to another location
		</note>
	</window>
	<music>
		<desc>
			How many times have you banged out a tune on the different colors of crystals? With your new device, you should be able to attain even greater musical fidelity, complete with greater range, chord capability, and even - somehow - an oddly familiar melody that came pre-etched into the crystal matrix.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</music>
	<turret>
		<desc>
			If you had an emerald for every time a creeper ambushed you right as you left your front door, you would have enough to be able to afford trading with villagers. Frustrated with this repeated occurrence, you have designed a small construct which can fire energy into nearby hostiles, ultimately killing them. Now all they need is a high-pitched voice and a polite demeanor...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a clear view of the sky and the target mob to function
		</note>
	</turret>
	<pylonturbo>
		<desc>
			You knew you could turbocharge your pylons, but that little display of yours, hopping up and down around the pylon, wildly flailing your manipulator, was neither insightful, productive, nor dignified. Now, however, the pattern is more clear: You need to enhance the structure, building a ring of 8 foci - and one central one below the pylon itself - and trigger the central one with your manipulator. Surely interrupting this process - or breaking the stabilization ring afterwards - is a very bad idea.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Ring: Requires a clear view of the sky and air around it to work; Center: Must be placed 8 blocks below the pylon's orb
		</note>
	</pylonturbo>
	<personal>
		<desc>
			Flying out to each of the sixteen colors of pylon to draw energy from them to power your abilities is a massive headache. Perhaps you could try to imitate them somehow. No doubt you lack the skill - or patience - required to duplicate them exactly, but the end result, if not able to be networked, might still serve as a useful charging point, as well as a nice decoration.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</personal>
	<cloaking>
		<desc>
			Rather inconveniently, you have found yourself largely confined to your base during the night, as it is your only defence against the waves of mobs, which lock onto you the moment you step outside. And this is not counting the time a horde of zombies, detecting the light of your constructions, made a beeline to you and destroyed most of the structure that stood in their way. After much frustration, it hit you: A cloaking device, which makes you undetectable unless at point-blank range. Pleasantly, it even smells of raspberries.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires the tower structure around it to focus its energy and function correctly
		</note>
	</cloaking>
	<lighter>
		<desc>
			Caves are an extremely unpleasant place to be - how many times have you found a large vein of ore, only to be shot into lava, fall down a gravel pit, or be dive-bombed by a creeper? - largely due to their cavernous gloom. Sure, you can cover the entire interior of the cave system with torches, but that quickly gets ridiculous, and after that incident with a gas pocket near the coal vein you wish for an alternative. Knowing that %s energy is that of light, you are sure you can use that to your advantage and make cave-mining actually enjoyable again.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</lighter>
	<reverter>
		<desc>
			Your world is slowly becoming corrupted. From pillars of obsidian that darken the world around them, to a purple weed that overtakes everything in sight, you find the once-beautiful landscape becoming ugly and inhospitable. Even the magic forests spread by the trees often make a mess of the biome. What you really need is a way to restore the biome to its former state.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reverter>
	<cobblegen>
		<desc>
			You never think you would run out of cobblestone...until you actually do. Sure, you could mine more out of the ground, but you have better things to occupy your time. You know that mixing water and lava will make cobblestone, but automating that process is messy and often costly. One solution would be a flower that would pull up the required liquid from nearby pools, mixing it and dropping the result. It might even be able to make things other than cobblestone given the correct input liquids.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cobblegen>
	<plantaccel>
		<desc>
			Like the proverbial grass and its glacial growth speed, your various flowers and plants to improve the area around them operate at a very slow pace. Perhaps they could be improved upon by being planted on a plant of its own.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</plantaccel>
	<cropspeed>
		<desc>
			Though some crops grow rapidly, the majority - even after careful crossbreeding and hours digging up weeds - very much do not. Already available to you are various means with which to increase that speed, but none of them fit neatly into the farm area itself, instead often requiring being placed nearby. This of course introduces an efficiency penalty, one that would be very desirable to avoid.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cropspeed>
	<inserter>
		<desc>
			You have repeatedly found yourself manually adding items to constructs that cannot be connected to normal item transport. You long ago tired of dropping stack after stack of sugar into a stone basin, or of berries into a puddle of chroma. You need a way to automate that process before you give up and find something less of a hassle to work with.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</inserter>
	<essentiarelay>
		<desc>
			So you have a cauldron full of water, in which you need to dump various ingredients to fabricate your desired target. As that process more often fails than not, producing copious amounts of noxious gas in the process, you created an odd construct to help automate the process. However, you need to actually transport the essentia there, and the piping you tried at first...leaves much to be desired. A longer-range and more flexible solution - ideally more consistently functional as well - would fare far better.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</essentiarelay>
	<glowfire>
		<desc>
			Some things you never have enough of, in particular diamonds, shards, and iron (the last of which was not helped by your attempts to build a turbine the size of a small house). Other things you have so much of that your biggest problem is storing it somewhere. What would be most convenient would be to be able to decompose the latter into energy with which you could cast the former. Surely nothing could go wrong with this...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</glowfire>
	<broadcast>
		<desc>
			You now regret living in a mountain archipelago. For one, most of the pylons to which you wish to connect are thousands of meters away. Worse, though, are that many are across vast stretches of ocean. Yes, you could build cobblestone pillars to raise repeaters from the ocean floor, but you want a solution that is both convenient and does not look ridiculous. To that end, you designed high-power broadcasters, which can send energy over thousands of blocks. However, such power requires a large structure, and that they would interfere if too close to each other.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</broadcast>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
</machines>