<?xml version="1.0"?>
<progression>
	<crystals>
		<title>
			Tangible Energy
		</title>
		<hint>
			Crystal energy is mostly an ethereal, intagible force. However, when concentrated, it may have a physical manifestation.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Sure enough, you have found places where crystal energy has coalesced and formed regular, glassy formations, ones that radiate the effects of their element.
		</reveal>
	</crystals>
	<casting>
		<title>
			Fabrication
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely the wooden crafting table is not sufficient to do all your crafting.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			As expected, to perform feats more complex than making a wooden box to store your items, you needed to create a special more magically-sound table.
		</reveal>
	</casting>
	<dyetree>
		<title>
			Technicolor Trees
		</title>
		<hint>
			These trees seem to come in all sorts of colors; you wonder if there is something special about them.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Well, they seem to drop berries and dyes of their color, so that has to count for something...
		</reveal>
	</dyetree>
	<multiblock>
		<title>
			More Complex Crafting
		</title>
		<hint>
			The more complex ideas you have could not possibly be pulled off with only nine constituent items...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Sure enough, the 5x5 afforded by the item stands is what you need.
		</reveal>
	</multiblock>
	<runeuse>
		<title>
			Weak Magical Foci
		</title>
		<hint>
			You may not be able to harness the power of the pylons yet, but these may make a milder alternative, allowing you to enhance your crafting capabilities.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That they do, allowing you to make items more infused with energy than simple stone.
		</reveal>
	</runeuse>
	<pylon>
		<title>
			Energy Beacons
		</title>
		<hint>
			Glowing and radiant, what are these?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Some sort of an energy beacon...probably a good idea to remember that.
		</reveal>
	</pylon>
	<link>
		<title>
			Top-tier Crafting
		</title>
		<hint>
			Finally you can harness the pylons, but how to put it to use?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Channeling all that energy directly into the table has allowed you to construct devices from your wildest imagination.
		</reveal>
	</link>
	<charge>
		<title>
			Energy Internalization
		</title>
		<hint>
			If the pylons and trees can store energy, maybe you can too...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Turns out you can, though the acquisition process is more dangerous than is enjoyable.
		</reveal>
	</charge>
	<ability>
		<title>
			Personal Enhancement
		</title>
		<hint>
			Machines you can accelerate. Tools you can enchant. Yourself?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A new set of rituals has given you abilities of great utility.
		</reveal>
	</ability>
	<rainbowleaf>
		<title>
			Magical Trees
		</title>
		<hint>
			Trees in various colors were one thing. But this?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The raw magic energy in this tree is palpable, not to mention behind the impressive visual display.
		</reveal>
	</rainbowleaf>
	<makechroma>
		<title>
			Magic Liquid
		</title>
		<hint>
			A collector, but of what, and from what?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Experience can be converted to a mysterious magic fluid. Surely that will have uses.
		</reveal>
	</makechroma>
	<shardcharge>
		<title>
			Enriching Solvent
		</title>
		<hint>
			The liquid is pulsing and throbbing with raw magical energy. You wonder what its effects are...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Dissolving berries in the chroma allows it to greatly boost the magic energy found in the crystal shards.
		</reveal>
	</shardcharge>
	<chroma>
		<title>
			Liquid Effects
		</title>
		<hint>
			Liquid chroma has already proven itself a solvent for items tossed in. What else might happen?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Stepping in it yourself seemed to do little - though you do feel a bit rejuvenated - but its power to enrich materials is not insignificant.
		</reveal>
	</chroma>
	<alloy>
		<title>
			Magic Alloying
		</title>
		<hint>
			What about mundane materials, perhaps with other materials mixed in?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The chroma dissolves those materials, infusing the mundane materials with a great deal of energy.
		</reveal>
	</alloy>
	<stones>
		<title>
			Unity of the Elements
		</title>
		<hint>
			What effect does combining all the different elements have?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			This gemstone throbs will all the colors of energy. That will surely prove useful.
		</reveal>
	</stones>
	<shock>
		<title>
			Damaging Discharge
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons seem friendly...are they?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			If your idea of "friendly" is a discharge to the face...
		</reveal>
	</shock>
	<nether>
		<title>
			The Evil Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			You need some other way below that unyielding rock...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			So those stories of obsidian portals leading to a fiery nightmare are true...
		</reveal>
	</nether>
	<end>
		<title>
			The Alien Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely nothing could be more alien than that land of lava, glowing stalactites, and flying jellyfish...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Apparently it can.
		</reveal>
	</end>
	<twilight>
		<title>
			The Forested Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			Legends tell of a different plane, covered in thick forests, with giant towers and buried mazes.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Not only does this realm exist, but it teems with unique creatures and is plentiful with treasure.
		</reveal>
	</twilight>
	<bedrock>
		<title>
			World Floor
		</title>
		<hint>
			Is it possible to dig too deep?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Maybe, but that layer of rock below seems impenetrable.
		</reveal>
	</bedrock>
	<cavern>
		<title>
			Buried Hollows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely many treasures lie underground.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Buried deep in the rock, these crystal-rich cavities hold further intrigue.
		</reveal>
	</cavern>
	<burrow>
		<title>
			Secret Burrows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Patches of light dot the night landscape; some are explainable as lava or fire, but not all...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Upon closer inspection, you found hidden burrows stocked with goods, but for who?
		</reveal>
	</burrow>
	<ocean>
		<title>
			Ocean Temples
		</title>
		<hint>
			Stories abound of strange structures left in the deepest parts of the ocean.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			True stories, it seems. If only they warned of the danger...
		</reveal>
	</ocean>
	<desertstruct>
		<title>
			Sandy Burrows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Aside from the rare (and explosive) pyramids, do deserts hold other secrets?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			They do indeed, and their riches eclipse most others.
		</reveal>
	</desertstruct>
	<die>
		<title>
			Painful Loss
		</title>
		<hint>
			You lose your items when you die; what happens to your knowledge?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Lost too. Ouch.
		</reveal>
	</die>
	<allcolors>
		<title>
			Elemental Awareness
		</title>
		<hint>
			Red, Green, Blue, Orange, how many are there?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			You have identified sixteen, each with a unique color and symbolic icon.
		</reveal>
	</allcolors>
	<repeater>
		<title>
			Broadcasting
		</title>
		<hint>
			Unless you set up dangerously close to a pylon, there does not seem to be a way to use them, as their range is too limited.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			These refractors of a sort seem to be able to reconcentrate and repeat the signal.
		</reveal>
	</repeater>
	<rainbowforest>
		<title>
			Magical Forests
		</title>
		<hint>
			You have heard rumors of forests populated with those brightly colored trees as far as the eye can see...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Not only do such forests exist, but they also teem with animals and plants, and the magic keeps hostile forces at bay.
		</reveal>
	</rainbowforest>
	<dimension>
		<title>
			Other Worlds
		</title>
		<hint>
			You have been to several other worlds, each stranger than the last...could there be more?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			There are indeed, but this one...is different.
		</reveal>
	</dimension>
	<ctm>
		<title>
			Restoration
		</title>
		<hint>
			A ruined structure. Scattered pieces.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The reward for completing and restoring the monument must be large.
		</reveal>
	</ctm>
	<storage>
		<title>
			Lumen Storage
		</title>
		<hint>
			Some constructs need to be moved around, making repeater-based power difficult. Is there an alternative?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Fortunately, you have found out how to store energy in a crystal matrix for exactly this purpose.
		</reveal>
	</storage>
	<balllightning>
		<title>
			Orbs of Energy
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons and some trees seem to spawn odd balls of energy.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			They do not seem particularly useful, but at least they are not obviously dangerous.
		</reveal>
	</balllightning>
	<powercrystal>
		<title>
			Recharge
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons drain too quickly for instensive use, and take too long to recharge.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That ring of iridescent crystals dramatically helps.
		</reveal>
	</powercrystal>
	<killdragon>
		<title>
			Aerial Predator
		</title>
		<hint>
			The static sky is empty...save for a massive dragon.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Killing it has revealed yet more of the world to you.
		</reveal>
	</killdragon>
	<breakspawner>
		<title>
			Endless Mobs
		</title>
		<hint>
			These metal cages spew forth endless creatures...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The only way to stop them is to destroy them.
		</reveal>
	</breakspawner>
	<killwither>
		<title>
			Eldritch Nightmare
		</title>
		<hint>
			Four soul sand. Three wither skulls. What could this possibly be useful for?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			An undead monstrosity, though its loot proved useful.
		</reveal>
	</killwither>
	<hive>
		<title>
			Crystal Hives
		</title>
		<hint>
			Can bees live in the darkness of underground caves?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, they can, and not only that, but they take on the effect of nearby cave crystals.
		</reveal>
	</hive>
	<killmob>
		<title>
			Monster Slayer
		</title>
		<hint>
			Certain creatures prove vicious, and will need to be dealt with.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Conveniently, they drop useful items when killed.
		</reveal>
	</killmob>
	<allcores>
		<title>
			Dimensional Cores
		</title>
		<hint>
			They come in various colors...what are they for?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			I have all sixteen...maybe these are for that monument I need to repair...
		</reveal>
	</allcores>
	<turbocharge>
		<title>
			Pylon Turbocharging
		</title>
		<hint>
			This should be possible...if somewhat violent.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			More so than expected, but also far more valuable.
		</reveal>
	</turbocharge>
	<useenergy>
		<title>
			Lumen Harnessing
		</title>
		<hint>
			If pylons are a source of energy, does that mean they can be used?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, and the myriad constructs powered by them offer great utility.
		</reveal>
	</useenergy>
	<structcomplete>
		<title>
			Unusual Structures
		</title>
		<hint>
			Large structures dot the volatile realm. What lies deep inside them?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A glowing core, tuned to one of the crystal colors. Interesting...
		</reveal>
	</structcomplete>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>

		</title>
		<hint>

		</hint>
		<reveal>

		</reveal>
	</name>
</progression>