<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<progression>
	<crystals>
		<title>
			Tangible Energy
		</title>
		<hint>
			Crystal energy is mostly an ethereal, intagible force. However, when concentrated, it may have a physical manifestation.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Sure enough, you have found places where crystal energy has coalesced and formed regular, glassy formations, ones that radiate the effects of their element.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Underground crystals of energy, radiating the effect of their element
		</desc>
	</crystals>
	<casting>
		<title>
			Fabrication
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely the wooden crafting table is not sufficient to do all your crafting.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			As expected, to perform feats more complex than making a wooden box to store your items, you needed to create a special more magically-sound table.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			To create anything remotely magical, you needed a dedicated, magically-capable table on which to do it
		</desc>
	</casting>
	<dyetree>
		<title>
			Technicolor Trees
		</title>
		<hint>
			These trees seem to come in all sorts of colors; you wonder if there is something special about them.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Well, they seem to drop berries and dyes of their color, so that has to count for something...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Trees, likely magical, of every color, and which drop not only saplings but dyes and berries
		</desc>
	</dyetree>
	<multiblock>
		<title>
			More Complex Crafting
		</title>
		<hint>
			The more complex ideas you have could not possibly be pulled off with only nine constituent items...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Sure enough, the 5x5 afforded by the item stands is what you need.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Using item stands has allowed you to expand the complexity of your crafting recipes
		</desc>
	</multiblock>
	<runeuse>
		<title>
			Weak Magical Foci
		</title>
		<hint>
			You may not be able to harness the power of the pylons yet, but these may make a milder alternative, allowing you to enhance your crafting capabilities.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That they do, allowing you to make items more infused with energy than simple stone.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			The beginnings of harnessing crystal energy, allowing you to enhance your crafting
		</desc>
	</runeuse>
	<pylon>
		<title>
			Energy Beacons
		</title>
		<hint>
			Glowing and radiant, what are these?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Some sort of an energy beacon...probably a good idea to remember that.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A source of crystal energy, almost dangerously powerful and of incalculable value
		</desc>
	</pylon>
	<link>
		<title>
			Top-tier Crafting
		</title>
		<hint>
			Finally you can harness the pylons, but how to put it to use?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Channeling all that energy directly into the table has allowed you to construct devices from your wildest imagination.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Crafting with lumen energy allows for the creation of powerful constructs
		</desc>
	</link>
	<charge>
		<title>
			Energy Internalization
		</title>
		<hint>
			If the pylons and trees can store energy, maybe you can too...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Turns out you can, though the acquisition process is more dangerous than is enjoyable.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Collecting energy in oneself to...do something
		</desc>
	</charge>
	<ability>
		<title>
			Personal Enhancement
		</title>
		<hint>
			Machines you can upgrade. Tools you can enchant. Yourself?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A new set of rituals has given you abilities of great utility.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Various powers and abilities offer huge potential
		</desc>
	</ability>
	<rainbowleaf>
		<title>
			Magical Trees
		</title>
		<hint>
			Trees in various colors were one thing. But this?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The raw magic energy in this tree is palpable, not to mention behind the impressive visual display.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A giant tree of iridescent hue. It surely has magic power that you can only imagine
		</desc>
	</rainbowleaf>
	<makechroma>
		<title>
			Magic Liquid
		</title>
		<hint>
			A collector, but of what, and from what?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Experience can be converted to a mysterious magic fluid. Surely that will have uses.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A distilled essence of experience, or magic, with as-yet unknown purpose
		</desc>
	</makechroma>
	<shardcharge>
		<title>
			Enriching Solvent
		</title>
		<hint>
			The liquid is pulsing and throbbing with raw magical energy. You wonder what its effects are...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Dissolving berries in the chroma allows it to greatly boost the magic energy found in the crystal shards.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Enhancing the power of a crystal shard with elemental energy distilled from the trees
		</desc>
	</shardcharge>
	<chroma>
		<title>
			Liquid Effects
		</title>
		<hint>
			Liquid chroma has already proven itself a solvent for items tossed in. What else might happen?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Stepping in it yourself seemed to do little - though you do feel a bit rejuvenated - but its power to enrich materials is not insignificant.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			This liquid has enriching power, and you have only scratched the surface
		</desc>
	</chroma>
	<alloy>
		<title>
			Magic Alloying
		</title>
		<hint>
			What about mundane materials, perhaps with other materials mixed in?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The chroma dissolves those materials, infusing the mundane materials with a great deal of energy.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			The creation of magical materials with the enriching power of liquid chroma
		</desc>
	</alloy>
	<stones>
		<title>
			Unity of the Elements
		</title>
		<hint>
			What effect does combining all the different elements have?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			This gemstone throbs will all the colors of energy. That will surely prove useful.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A complete collection of the crystal elements into a gem
		</desc>
	</stones>
	<shock>
		<title>
			Damaging Discharge
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons seem friendly...are they?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			If your idea of "friendly" is a discharge to the face...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Proximity to a crystal pylon, at least for now, is clearly undesirable
		</desc>
	</shock>
	<nether>
		<title>
			The Evil Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			You need some other way below that unyielding rock...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			So those stories of obsidian portals leading to a fiery nightmare are true...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A hostile, unpleasant world of lava, red rock, and nightmarish creatures
		</desc>
	</nether>
	<end>
		<title>
			The Alien Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely nothing could be more alien than that land of lava, glowing stalactites, and flying jellyfish...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Apparently it can.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A...strange world suspended in the void, ruled by an aggressive dragon
		</desc>
	</end>
	<twilight>
		<title>
			The Forested Realm
		</title>
		<hint>
			Legends tell of a different plane, covered in thick forests, with giant towers and buried mazes.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Not only does this realm exist, but it teems with unique creatures and is plentiful with treasure.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A mystical forest dotted with massive structures and strange creatures
		</desc>
	</twilight>
	<bedrock>
		<title>
			World Floor
		</title>
		<hint>
			Is it possible to dig too deep?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Maybe, but that layer of rock below seems impenetrable.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			An unyielding barrier to those who attempt to dig downwards
		</desc>
	</bedrock>
	<cavern>
		<title>
			Buried Hollows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Surely many treasures lie underground.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Buried deep in the rock, these crystal-rich cavities hold further intrigue.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A buried room, populated with crystals and some random loot
		</desc>
	</cavern>
	<burrow>
		<title>
			Secret Burrows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Patches of light dot the night landscape; some are explainable as lava or fire, but not all...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Upon closer inspection, you found hidden burrows stocked with goods, but for who?
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A small burrow, with a handful of starter items
		</desc>
	</burrow>
	<ocean>
		<title>
			Ocean Temples
		</title>
		<hint>
			Stories abound of strange structures left in the deepest parts of the ocean.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			True stories, it seems. If only they warned of the danger...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A large submerged structure which is more complex than it first appears
		</desc>
	</ocean>
	<desertstruct>
		<title>
			Sandy Burrows
		</title>
		<hint>
			Aside from the rare (and explosive) pyramids, do deserts hold other secrets?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			They do indeed, and their riches eclipse most others.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A subsurface hollow, filled with loot but also danger
		</desc>
	</desertstruct>
	<snowstruct>
		<title>
			Snowy Outposts
		</title>
		<hint>
			Snow and ice as far as the eye can see, and yet there remain things to find.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Including, it seems, long-abandoned outposts holding...something.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A rich discovery in a desolate arctic wasteland
		</desc>
	</snowstruct>
	<die>
		<title>
			Painful Loss
		</title>
		<hint>
			You lose your items when you die; what happens to your knowledge?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Lost too. Ouch.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Like your items, your knowledge and energy is also lost upon your demise
		</desc>
	</die>
	<allcolors>
		<title>
			Elemental Awareness
		</title>
		<hint>
			Red, Green, Blue, Orange, how many are there?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			You have identified sixteen, each with a unique color and symbolic icon.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Sixteen colors, sixteen forms of energy, each tuned to a specific property
		</desc>
	</allcolors>
	<repeater>
		<title>
			Broadcasting
		</title>
		<hint>
			You need a better way to transfer lumen energy from the pylons to your base.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			These refractors of a sort seem to be able to reconcentrate and repeat the signal.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A more refined and effective form of lumen transmission
		</desc>
	</repeater>
	<rainbowforest>
		<title>
			Magical Forests
		</title>
		<hint>
			You have heard rumors of forests populated with those brightly colored trees as far as the eye can see...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Not only do such forests exist, but they also teem with animals and plants, and the magic keeps hostile forces at bay.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A magic forest, full of multicolored trees and with significant power to keep evil away
		</desc>
	</rainbowforest>
	<glowcliffs>
		<title>
			Glowing Terraces
		</title>
		<hint>
			Are all the magical areas in this world forests? Might there be rare exceptions?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Every level of this strange new place seems to contain novel phenomena, resources, or flora.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Large terraced cliffs, with a distinctly unusual ambience
		</desc>
	</glowcliffs>
	<dimension>
		<title>
			Other Worlds
		</title>
		<hint>
			You have been to several other worlds, each stranger than the last...could there be more?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			There are indeed, but this one...is different.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A new world...strange, yet peaceful and serene. And vibrantly hued
		</desc>
	</dimension>
	<ctm>
		<title>
			Restoration
		</title>
		<hint>
			A ruined structure. Scattered pieces.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The reward for completing and restoring the monument must be large.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Completing the ruined monument, with surely significant reward
		</desc>
	</ctm>
	<storage>
		<title>
			Lumen Storage
		</title>
		<hint>
			Some constructs need to be moved around, making repeater-based power difficult. Is there an alternative?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Fortunately, you have found out how to store energy in a crystal matrix for exactly this purpose.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Storing energy in a crystal for easy mobility
		</desc>
	</storage>
	<balllightning>
		<title>
			Orbs of Energy
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons and some trees seem to spawn odd balls of energy.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			They do not seem particularly useful, but at least they are not obviously dangerous.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A glowing, moving clump of energy that seems to be animated on its own
		</desc>
	</balllightning>
	<powercrystal>
		<title>
			Recharge
		</title>
		<hint>
			Pylons drain too quickly for intensive use, and take too long to recharge.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That ring of iridescent crystals dramatically helps.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Upgrading a pylon with a ring of eight power crystals massively improves its energy recovery
		</desc>
	</powercrystal>
	<killdragon>
		<title>
			Aerial Predator
		</title>
		<hint>
			The static sky is empty...save for a massive dragon.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Killing it has revealed yet more of the world to you.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A giant, hostile dragon whose destruction gives both physical and conceptual reward
		</desc>
	</killdragon>
	<findspawner>
		<title>
			Endless Mobs
		</title>
		<hint>
			What is that strange flaming box?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A construct of some malevolent origin, a source for an interminable stream of creatures.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Strange metal boxes that release infinite numbers of monsters
		</desc>
	</findspawner>
	<breakspawner>
		<title>
			Stopping the Torrent
		</title>
		<hint>
			These metal cages spew forth endless creatures...how to put an end to it?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The only way to stop them is to destroy them...for now.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Destroying a spawner not only stops the flood of creatures, but also lets you better understand, and maybe even harvest it
		</desc>
	</breakspawner>
	<killwither>
		<title>
			Eldritch Nightmare
		</title>
		<hint>
			Four soul sand. Three wither skulls. What could this possibly be useful for?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			An undead monstrosity, though its loot proved useful.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A nightmarish creature which drops a mysterious but obviously valuable star
		</desc>
	</killwither>
	<hive>
		<title>
			Crystal Hives
		</title>
		<hint>
			Can bees live in the darkness of underground caves?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, they can, and not only that, but they take on the effect of nearby cave crystals.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Underground, crystalline hives full of uniquely adapted bees
		</desc>
	</hive>
	<killmob>
		<title>
			Monster Slayer
		</title>
		<hint>
			Certain creatures prove vicious, and will need to be dealt with.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Conveniently, they drop useful items when killed.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Killing various creatures, especially hostile ones, drops an assortment of useful items
		</desc>
	</killmob>
	<allcores>
		<title>
			Dimensional Cores
		</title>
		<hint>
			They come in various colors...what are they for?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			I have all sixteen...maybe these are for that monument I need to repair...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Collecting all sixteen glowing orbs, for some unified purpose
		</desc>
	</allcores>
	<turbocharge>
		<title>
			Pylon Turbocharging
		</title>
		<hint>
			This should be possible...if somewhat violent.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			More so than expected, but also far more valuable.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Greatly enhancing the power of a crystal pylon
		</desc>
	</turbocharge>
	<useenergy>
		<title>
			Lumen Harnessing
		</title>
		<hint>
			If pylons are a source of energy, does that mean they can be used?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, and the myriad constructs powered by them offer great utility.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Relaying the signal from a crystal pylon allows for feasible use of their energy
		</desc>
	</useenergy>
	<structcomplete>
		<title>
			Unusual Structures
		</title>
		<hint>
			Large structures dot the volatile realm. What lies deep inside them?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A glowing core, tuned to one of the crystal colors. Interesting...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Completing the task in the strange construction, and being consequently rewarded
		</desc>
	</structcomplete>
	<netherroof>
		<title>
			A second layer
		</title>
		<hint>
			The evil realm seems capped. Is the cap impenetrable?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			No, and further mysteries await for those who venture into it.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Getting above the impassable layer at the top of the Nether
		</desc>
	</netherroof>
	<netherstruct>
		<title>
			Ominous Constructions
		</title>
		<hint>
			Strange things dot and cross the Nether roof.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Some even contain useful clues.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Finding the secrets buried in the Nether
		</desc>
	</netherstruct>
	<villagecasting>
		<title>
			A...less than honorable attempt
		</title>
		<hint>
			Are you the only one to have tried to learn these magic forces?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			No, but the others who tried have clearly been about as smart as a piece of flint.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			The villagers have tried - and abjectly failed - to learn to manipulate crystal energy.
		</desc>
	</villagecasting>
	<anystruct>
		<title>
			Buried Ruins
		</title>
		<hint>
			From cobblestone squares to ancient mines, it appears some have come before you; have they left anything else?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, including their attempts to learn the same things you now attempt.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Buried structures, clearly of artificial origin
		</desc>
	</anystruct>
	<focuscrystal>
		<title>
			Refractory Gems
		</title>
		<hint>
			You have thought of a way to increase the power of your fabrication constructs, but what to use as a refractor?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Who would have thought THEY had found the key...
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Crude 'refining' of emeralds into a useful construct
		</desc>
	</focuscrystal>
	<artefact>
		<title>
			Mysterious Relics
		</title>
		<hint>
			All around the world linger remnants of...something.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Including particularly mysterious - and dangerous - ones found in certain regions.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A strange buried artifact, surely possessing secrets
		</desc>
	</artefact>
	<tower>
		<title>
			Glowing Towers
		</title>
		<hint>
			The pylons are not the only luminous constructs you find around the world.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The purpose these obelisks serve is a entirely unknown, but they must be key to something.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			An ancient structure, topped with a luminescent...something.
		</desc>
	</tower>
	<blowrepeater>
		<title>
			Lumen Overload
		</title>
		<hint>
			These wooden lumen foci seem to work quite well...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			...Except when they explode trying.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Wood and chroma repeaters might have been a mistake
		</desc>
	</blowrepeater>
	<chargecrystal>
		<title>
			Lumen Storage II
		</title>
		<hint>
			A storage crystal is little more than a pretty rock without a way to put the energy into it.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			As is usual, a simple problem has a simple - and spinny - solution.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Putting energy into a storage crystal
		</desc>
	</chargecrystal>
	<structcheat>
		<title>
			Finding a shortcut
		</title>
		<hint>
			You may have the means to attempt to bypass the strange structures you find.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			With disastrous results. Whoever designed those structures is clearly more resourceful than you are.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Or not.
		</desc>
	</structcheat>
	<voidmonster>
		<title>
			A distortion below the world
		</title>
		<hint>
			Exactly what that thing is, remains unknown.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Some sort of foreboding corruption of reality.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A corruption of reality itself
		</desc>
	</voidmonster>
	<voidmonsterdie>
		<title>
			Contact with the corruption
		</title>
		<hint>
			What could possibly go wrong?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That thing must now be destroyed after what it has done to you.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Death by amorphous evil
		</desc>
	</voidmonsterdie>
	<luma>
		<title>
			Ethereal Luma
		</title>
		<hint>
			Some essence...of...something?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The essence of the void, of space, as well as lumen energy.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A liquid of both energy and space
		</desc>
	</luma>
	<warpnode>
		<title>
			Energy Vortices
		</title>
		<hint>
			Some sort of hole in space.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Which may provide a method to travel between them.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Wormholes of a sort
		</desc>
	</warpnode>
	<powertree>
		<title>
			Stockpiling Energy
		</title>
		<hint>
			A construct which has the ability to draw lumens into itself...for what?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Apparently to act as a large buffer or storage.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Arboriform Battery
		</desc>
	</powertree>
	<tunecast>
		<title>
			Casting Personalization
		</title>
		<hint>
			How to imprint yourself onto your casting structure?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That should have been rather obvious in hindsight.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Linking your crafting to your person
		</desc>
	</tunecast>
	<bypassweak>
		<title>
			Retroactive Recognition
		</title>
		<hint>
			This particular design seems somewhat familiar, and not in a good way.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Prediction of upcoming mistakes enables you to avoid them altogether.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Spotting disaster before it strikes
		</desc>
	</bypassweak>
	<infuse>
		<title>
			Resourceful Experience
		</title>
		<hint>
			Can one even combine such disparate things as items, liquids, and players?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			As with most things, all it took was the proper construct.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Imbuing one energy into another
		</desc>
	</infuse>
	<pylonlink>
		<title>
			Energy Interconnection
		</title>
		<hint>
			You can connect one pylon to a network, but that still leaves all the others...
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Linking them together makes for a much larger energy pool and recharge rate.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A way to make use of multiple pylons per color
		</desc>
	</pylonlink>
	<relays>
		<title>
			Compact Transmission
		</title>
		<hint>
			Not all constructs are amenable to normal energy transfer, being used indoors or in large numbers.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Fortunately, they seem to be receptive to a scaled-down and more orthogonal method of conduction.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Transmitting energy in confined spaces
		</desc>
	</relays>
	<energyidea>
		<title>
			Refined Transmission
		</title>
		<hint>
			Wood and chroma repeaters are of marginal quality.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			And these crystals surely hold the key to something better.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Insight into lumen transmission
		</desc>
	</energyidea>
	<node>
		<title>
			Energy Inlet
		</title>
		<hint>
			Where does this aspect-based energy originate?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			That remains unknown, but it leaks in via tiny holes.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A source of unusual energy
		</desc>
	</node>
	<potion>
		<title>
			Ambient Effects
		</title>
		<hint>
			Can I improve my various powers, without tools?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Yes, and this may only be the start.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Augmenting personal capabilities
		</desc>
	</potion>
	<mine>
		<title>
			Resource Acquisition
		</title>
		<hint>
			Where can I find the raw materials to begin?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			Many different ores populate the world.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			The source of many of the raw materials.
		</desc>
	</mine>
	<deepcave>
		<title>
			Lower Layers
		</title>
		<hint>
			Cave systems seem to extend far below the surface.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The deeper I go, the more exotic the things I find.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Venturing ever deeper
		</desc>
	</deepcave>
	<harvest>
		<title>
			Crop Collection
		</title>
		<hint>
			Some materials are mined, and others grown.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The latter includes a wide variety.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Producing resources on demand
		</desc>
	</harvest>
	<myst>
		<title>
			A Scripted World
		</title>
		<hint>
			I can create worlds out of words.
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			And these words describe novel features and resources.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Constructed by a story
		</desc>
	</myst>
	<biomestruct>
		<title>
			An Abandoned Puzzle
		</title>
		<hint>
			What might be found in the more magically-attuned biomes?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			A structure that once completed, contains far more riches than any other so far.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			A structure in a magic forest, locked down behind tests of skill
		</desc>
	</biomestruct>
	<farlands>
		<title>
			Outer Regions
		</title>
		<hint>
			Is this world the same forever?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			No, areas distant from the entry point contain novel formations, materials, and...others.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			New areas in a new world
		</desc>
	</farlands>
	<mudhint>
		<title>
			Magical Residue
		</title>
		<hint>
			Can magical materials be found naturally? What happens when large amounts congregate? Does this stuff break down over time?
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			The debris falling off of rainbow trees accumulates and creates a muddy substance below.
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			Residue of magical substances
		</desc>
	</mudhint>
	<name>
		<title>
			
		</title>
		<hint>
			
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>
			
		</title>
		<hint>
			
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
	</name>
	<name>
		<title>
			
		</title>
		<hint>
			
		</hint>
		<reveal>
			
		</reveal>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
	</name>
</progression>
