<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<resource>
	<shards>
		Crystals cannot be easily harvested; when they are broken, they drop shards, which only have traces of the magic contained in the original crystal. Nonetheless, they are your primary substrate for other materials.
	</shards>
	<dusts>
		As you have become better acquainted with the nature of the crystal elements, you have become able to notice plants scattered around the landscape. No doubt they hold some of the secrets you need. It is probably best to use something like Fortune to make best use of them, while others might be able to be farmed.
	</dusts>
	<groups>
		Rarely are individual elements used in final construction procedures; more often, several or even all colors need to work in harmony. To accomplish this, you will find yourself joining, fusing, and otherwise restructuring the shards.
	</groups>
	<ores>
		With your increased knowledge and understanding, patches of rock that you once mistook for smooth stone now reveal themselves to you. Harvesting these is of obvious importance, as is using high-yield tools and enchantments to get the most out of them.
	</ores>
	<crystalstone>
		All the magic structures you have found thus far have been built of a smooth, dark stone, so it must be able to channel and conduct crystal energy. To that end, all of your constructions will probably use this material. It can be reshaped at will, and reverted back to the smooth variant with the application of heat.
	</crystalstone>
	<seed>
		Searching for and harvesting crystals is often a tedious task; however, you have found a way to imbue the magic off of the shards onto a plant, turning it into a brillant crystal flower that, while mostly for decoration, also provides a slight boost to your shard supplies. Perhaps you can find a way to improve them further still...
	</seed>
	<fragment>
		Scattered around the world are scraps of information on the fundamental elements of the universe, that is, the laws on which it operates. Combining those and some of your own research, you should be able to form a complete enough understanding so as to allow you to devise applications for those laws to suit your needs. Fragments can be added to your lexicon by opening the book while sneaking.
	</fragment>
	<berries>
		When harvesting the colored trees from around the world, you noticed that in addition to saplings and apples, they drop berries of the same color. They are too foul-tasting to be of much use for sustenance, but you can feel the tingle of energy contained within, making them a viable way to augment your own energy stores. They may also play a key role in enriching the power of crystal shards, though you will need some magical solvent.
	</berries>
	<cores>
		Some constructs need to perform special functions, like transforming their surroundings or opening a hole to the void. In order to do this, they will need to contain an appropriate core.
	</cores>
	<irid>
		You have already figured out that you can purify and then infuse shards with the essence of chroma. Now you can assemble them into larger parts which will ultimately be used to make the Power Crystals.
	</irid>
	<augment>
		The constructs running on the energy stored in crystals are useful to be sure, but you wonder if they are running at peak performance. In particular, you may be able to reduce their energy consumption, increase their speed, and for the mining device, get a product usable in that ore processing contraption that seems to quintuple the yield.
	</augment>
	<alloys>
		Much like how raw metals can be combined to yield materials of superior properties, you suspect that you can try the same with base metals like iron and gold to augment their characteristics, not for strength, but to imbue them with magic energy. Obviously, liquid chroma will be needed.
	</alloys>
	<bees>
		After being told that you could breed bees that make rare metals (how, exactly?), you let yourself be overcome with avarice and immediately ventured to do so. However, the things are unbelievably fussy, refusing to work in the rain, in the dark, with the slightest fluctuations in temperature, and on top of that work slowly and in a small area. Maybe you can improve their stock with outside genes.
	</bees>
	<hicores>
		The various crystal cores you have learned to craft are useful to be sure, but they lack...something. You could create higher-energy variants, but doing so would likely be a rather involved task, one not to be taken lightly.
	</hicores>
	<tinkertools>
		You already have found how to make mix-and-match tools from whatever material you please, how to upgrade them, and repair them. You even can put moss on them to make them repair themselves. However, that is ugly and slow. So you tried making one of Chromastone, hoping it would have self-repair as an innate capability...and try as you might, you could not squeeze Chromastone ingots into the wooden or brass part frames. Between mutterings of "but it worked for everyone else" and musings over why the creator must hate you so much, you realized another way to craft them.
	</tinkertools>
	<fertilityseed>
		You have noticed that the luminous roots found on some stone overhangs drop the occasional clump of seeds. This is not so much of a surprise - and at least these seeds do not make you feel like you snorted a sand block and sprayed your eyes with lava - but the effect these seeds have when dropped into plant material - especially grass and crops - is another matter altogether.
	</fertilityseed>
	<branches>
		-Unimplemented-
	</branches>
	<artefact>
		In certain regions of the world, you seem to be able to rarely find an odd, star-shaped...thing buried just below the surface. It has proven actively dangerous to carry, and the villagers you sold it to learned that the hard way (though the profit you earned doing so makes that something of a non-issue in your eyes). Whatever it is, and whoever made it, you probably do not want to get too many of these in one place, or to let them get too close to fragile technology...
	</artefact>
	<inscription>
		Scattered around the world - far more rarely than the pylons they slightly resemble - are towers, crested with a crystal that glows brightly and which seems to contain information inside its ordered structure. That is all well and good, but you might be able to use the crystal as a makeshift chisel as well, carving designs into stone for...something. It will probably have other more...refined uses as well.
	</inscription>
	<proxessence>
		This dust seems to have some sort of resonant property, almost like it is a tangible form of the world in which you found it. One wonders what significance that might have...
	</proxessence>
	<voidessence>
		How exactly one harms a malformation in the fabric of reality may be beyond your ability to comprehend, but the effects of doing this very much are not; when damaged the corruption seems to shed small pieces of itself, which weakly exhibit the same life-sucking abilities of the larger entity. You could of course use these to produce your own lethal constructions, but perhaps you could do something more creative with it...
	</voidessence>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
</resource>
