<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tools>
	<wand>
		The manipulator is your first foray into this strange new field of crystal elements and chromatic forces. The tool seems to be your main way of activating blocks, either to start some operation or to change settings on a device. It also seems capable of testing the connectivity of segments of a crystal network, and drawing energy off a pylon into yourself. Because of its strong link to your person, it will not work for other users, nor will it fare well in constructs designed to imitate you.
	</wand>
	<finder>
		The pylon compass scans the energy field that permeates the world and analyzes it to calculate the location of the nearest pylon of each crystal element. Due to the fact that the energy is always in flux, there is some inaccuracy to the calculation, but the location you are directed to should be within a short walk of the actual pylon.
	</finder>
	<excavator>
		By concentrating elements associated with energy and minerals, you have found that you can apply them to the terrain and excavate a large area. When you release the energy into the ground, it seems to only get conducted along identical materials, but this nonetheless allows you to clear a large area of rock, ores, or other materials with a single stroke. To avoid accidentally creating large holes, making it unable to mine the basic stone of the world is probably for the best.
	</excavator>
	<transition>
		Gray-colored energy seems to have the power to transmute and change, so it is a reasonable guess to think that if applied to the world, with some information of what blocks to place and replace, this power could be used to change large swaths of one block into another, greatly expediting the landscaping process.
	</transition>
	<invlink>
		<desc>
			Mining and other activities tend to fill your inventory with useless junk that seems to accumulate faster than you can get rid of it. By leveraging the power of elements associated with movement, you discover that you can create a linkage between your inventory and one placed somewhere in the world, and one for which you can control the items it transports.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Can be toggled to reverse the item flow direction
		</notes>
	</invlink>
	<pendant>
		<desc>
			As you have already discovered, crystallized elemental energy can be found scattered around the world, and its proximity imbues the effects of that element on yourself. However, the effect is rather less than convenient to transport in a form that bulky, so a logical next step would be to wear a small part of the crystal to allow you to benefit from its effects at any location.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			In some cases, this may alter the specific nature of the application of the effect
			
			Higher tiers of pendant emulate similarly higher tiers of placed crystals
		</notes>
	</pendant>
	<vacuumgun>
		Though purely utilitarian ways of killing hostile mobs get the job done, they lack a certain entertainment value. With that in mind, you devised a weapon that creates a rift in the fabric of space, pulling all the creatures into it from a substantial radius. Even better, it seems to rip the blocks out of the ground as well.
	</vacuumgun>
	<lens>
		Crystal Lenses work much like their optical counterparts, focusing, tinting, and otherwise manipulating a beam of energy so that it can apply its effects more strongly over a smaller area.
	</lens>
	<storage>
		Merging small amounts of all the types of crystal yields a crystal that seems to have the ability to store large amounts of energy delivered to it, almost like a battery. This may be convenient for some things that drain this energy yet are too portable for a true crystal network.
	</storage>
	<linktool>
		Many constructs come in pairs, needing to be linked to each other. The linking tool accomplishes exactly that, binding together two positions.
	</linktool>
	<warp>
		<desc>
			By experimenting with the darker aspects of another branch of magic, you have suffered some serious consequences, including impaired vision and a nasty tendency for the air around you to come alive with hostile and destructive manifestations of that power. With this mixture, you should be able to work towards keeping those effects at bay.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Requires activation to be useful
		</notes>
	</warp>
	<duplicator>
		Building structures that consist of many repeated parts is a tedious task involving less in the way mental vigour and more in the way of running around. Finally, however, you have found a way to scan regions of a structure and allow it to be replicated as many times as you see fit and can afford.
	</duplicator>
	<teleport>
		Long-distance travel has often been a major headache for you, and even with more advanced powers like gliding and flight, you find yourself spending a great deal of time in transit between distant locations. With the mobility wand, you can fling yourself at a distant location, appearing there instantaneously.
	</teleport>
	<builder>
		Building walls and paths is tedious and time-consuming. Fortunately, with the aid of the construction wand, you can extend any continuous surface you like, greatly expediting this process.
	</builder>
	<capture>
		Moving creatures is nearly impossible. Cows and other animals can be led with food, but they are so stupid that they frequently forget you exist and go wander off a cliff. Wolves have trouble telling the difference between water and lava - which would not be so much of a problem if not for their love of swimming - and cannot find their way through a door if their life depends on it. Finally, most hostile mobs would rather eat/shoot/explode your face than chase you hundreds of blocks. With the capture wand, however, you can ignore these obstacles and carry the mob - in suspension of course - wherever you need.
	</capture>
	<voidcell>
		Your mining efforts have yielded you untold riches in the form of metals, gems, and other materials, but it has also left you with mountains of stone - you literally could build a mountain if you felt like it. Being something of a pack rat, you cannot bring yourself to throw it away, and your crystal-based item storage system is rapidly approaching capacity with some 196 million of it. After some time spent reverse-engineering it, you hit upon a solution. Like the crystal tanks, you could probably use a void link to store basically infinite quantities of an item, though only one item per storage unit.
	</voidcell>
	<aurapouch>
		<desc>
			There are a great many tools available to you to grant you exceptional abilities, including those crystalline pendants you designed earlier. However, each of these needs to remain in your inventory to function. The end result is that your inventory quickly fills while mining, something not helped by the twenty kinds of stone you find underground. Putting these items in a backpack negates their effects, so that is not a solution, either. If only there was some way to put all these items in a bag and still have it pass on the items' effects...
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Individual slots can be toggled to temporarily negate both effects and lumen consumption
			
			In addition to standard "keep it in your inventory" items, some items which normally require being held or manually used may continue to work in the pouch:
		</notes>
	</aurapouch>
	<multitool>
		Different kinds of blocks need different kinds of tools to harvest them efficiently and effectively. Given the wide variety of blocks you come across, this quickly necessitates several tools - picks, axes, shovels, shears, your SWORD - and switching between them becomes increasingly clumsy. Combining all the tools into one - somehow - is the obvious solution.
	</multitool>
	<orepick>
		<desc>
			Branch mining is a waste of time. You make a narrow tunnel out of kilometers of rock and find barely anything - and most of what you find is worthless - except that which you blindly dug right into. No doubt large amounts of ore remain hidden to you just underneath the walls of your tunnel, but short of expending the herculean effort to clear all of the overlying stone, you will never know what you are missing...
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Can passively detect nearby ore behind walls, scan an ore vein's shape and size, or "ping" for ores in a large radius
		</notes>
	</orepick>
	<oresilk>
		You have mechanisms to process ore and increase your rate of return, from half a dozen ways of doubling it to ways of increasing that output even further, but this is rather unhelpful if the ore blocks themselves are unobtainable to you and the ore taunts you by dropping its contents instead. You could of course put Silk Touch on your tool, but enchanting is a random and often frustrating endeavor; a better idea would be to make the tool itself carve ore cleanly from the ground.
	</oresilk>
	<bulkmover>
		You often find yourself scrambling to load many items into a chest that feeds into a machine. The amount of work involved is tedious and frustrating, and a way to expedite the process would be most convenient. The item mover can do just that; it can move large quantities - up to ten thousand - of any one item at a time from one inventory (or digital storage system) to another.
	</bulkmover>
	<chaingun>
		Swords and arrows are useful to a point, but they quickly become insufficient if the target creatures are spread over too large an area. Fortunately, the chain gun can fire a projectile that bounces between multiple creatures, even across significant distances.
	</chaingun>
	<splash>
		For groups of tightly packed mobs, the usual strategy is to wildly flail a sword around you, but this is both rather amateur and ineffective. A weapon that dealt splash damage would be ideal...
	</splash>
	<endercrys>
		<desc>
			You recall needing eight of those mysterious pulsing crystals from the eldritch island, but attempting to interact with them blew up in your face...literally. You need a more delicate method of picking them up and storing them.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Can store multiple crystals
		</notes>
	</endercrys>
	<hover>
		Water buckets, as a method of breaking fall damage, are somewhat effective, but they require agile reflexes. As a way of climbing a wall, they are slow. Perhaps some sort of magical buffer would do a better job...
	</hover>
	<growth>
		Crops take forever to grow. Sure, wheat and that plant with the oily black seeds seem to grow fast enough, but things like sugar cane take hours, and those crops you got to (somehow) drop mob drops and bits of ore take so long you wonder if farming them is even worth the time. You had a watering can which seemed to help, but it got crumpled beyond recognition the moment you tried it with that automated clicking machine. You know that Kijani energy forms the basis of natural things, including plants; perhaps a blast of that may expedite the process.
	</growth>
	<doorkey>
		Doors are generally useless without keys. To that end, your ethereal barrier needs a key. After shift-right-clicking the key on the door, you linked the two and now using the key will open the door. Surely this key cannot open someone else's door.
	</doorkey>
	<ownerkey>
		You are sharing your house with a friend, but when they tried to use any of your constructions, from the %s to the %s, all they got in return was a clear message of "not yours". Time to rectify this.
	</ownerkey>
	<crystalcell>
		A great many types of items come in sixteen variants, one for each color of crystal energy. Sure, you could just dump them all into your magical etched-crystal storage device, but after mining out a dungeon and finding 23 different tools of six materials (who leaves a bronze sword in a random area underground?), the limit on item types is becoming insurmountable. Perhaps a storage cell dedicated to these crystalline items would mitigate the issue.
	</crystalcell>
	<purify>
		In some worlds, ranging from the Nether to some you concocted from ink and paper in an enormous display of greed, the magical effects of the crystals are corrupted, and twisted into dangerous and otherwise hostile forms. You would far prefer to be able to repair and purify that aura than flee everytime you hear a dinging noise in such places, not least because half the time that means off a cliff...into lava.
	</purify>
	<efficiency>
		Your new personal enhancements greatly increase your capabilities, but keeping their energy costs satisfied can get time-consuming and expensive. Recalling the kuro pendants, you consider making an enhanced version.
	</efficiency>
	<killaura>
		Amazingly, up until now you have been out of options for attacking a mob whose position you know but which you cannot see. Sure, you could break the barrier, but far better would be to simply attack them through walls. Accuracy, however, is not your strength, and the attack power can suffer for it.
	</killaura>
	<floatboots>
		Much to your chagrin, it seems nearly every build you make requires that you hover at some arbitrary distance off the ground, at neither the ceiling nor the floor, and not even at the right height for a pillar of dirt to help. You could use the flying attachment to your chestplate, but hovering in one place burns an excessive amount of fuel. With that in mind, you recall the floating stone deposits in the world you recently visited; They may be exactly what you need. Attaching some floatstone to your boots - whatever type they may be - will not only grant you the ability to hover, but dampen any fall.
	</floatboots>
	<beeframe>
		Bee breeding is slow. VERY slow. Sure, you have it easier now that you have a magic bronze box in which you can mash bees or their genes together and avoid the finicky nature of chance, but you still have to wait for the bees' lifecycle, something that often takes hours. Purple void frames are not common enough to be of much help, but maybe you can try making your own frames...
	</beeframe>
	<telecapsule>
		<desc>
			You have gotten lost so many times that you probably have more resources sitting in random "when you return" chests than you have back at home, and now you have done it again. Fed up with this, you have created a tablet that will let you instantly warp back to where you inscribed it. However, you appear to have done a rather poor job of it, as the thing is nearly as dangerous as teleporting blindly and hoping you do not end up suffocating in a wall. At least you are free of those damn gas and lava pockets...
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Maximum travel range of %dm
		</notes>
	</telecapsule>
	<caveexit>
		<desc>
			The first days of building a base are inevitably bottlenecked by the acquisition of ores, even with the help of your various machines to grind, pulverize, mill, or otherwise process them to increase the yield. And that means mining. Lots of mining. Branch mining is boring and unproductive, so you recently took up cave mining...something which is now a clear mistake, given your tendency to get lost in the deepest layers. You may not know the way back out, but perhaps you can create something that can...
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Can also be used in an alternate mode to find the deepest part of a cave system
		</notes>
	</caveexit>
	<mobsonar>
		The problem with caving, aside from the occasional pitfall into a ravine - and those should be avoidable by not being an idiot - is that no matter what you do, you are always forced to turn blind corners that more often than not hide one or more monsters who wish to kill you. You did have a radar you tried a while back, but its range was limited and your attempt at a moving version saw you exiled to another part of the world entirely. Perhaps you can try something more like sonar instead, this time without being accused of trying to gain unfair advantages by seeing that which you should not.
	</mobsonar>
	<structfind>
		You already know about the buried - slightly and deeply - structures in various biomes, from which you have learned the bulk of your knowledge of manipulating crystal energy. However, when it comes time to look for a new one, you thus far have had to rely on sheer luck, which is neither enjoyable nor productive. If you could tap into the ambient energy field the structures seem to focus on, you might help expedite that search.
	</structfind>
	<splineattack>
		As noted before, clusters of enemies are the most difficult arrangement to deal with, as focusing your attacks on one often mean being attacked by another with impunity. What you need is some sort of attack that can bridge the gap and jump between mobs, attacking them in rapid succession. And now you have it, though for some insane reason you keep getting asked if you need to whistle to use it.
	</splineattack>
	<shieldedcell>
		Those star-shaped things you found do not seem to mix well with electrical hardware. Indeed, to your horror, putting them in your crystal-based storage network caused the entire system to experience cascading failures. Some time ago, you DID pass a villager who offered a 'shielded' storage unit, but the idiot first demanded you venture 5000 blocks into the middle of nowhere, and asked for the smashed remains of some of the very items you want to store. Screw him and his device; you will create your own superior version, no fetch quests for random items or to random places required.
	</shieldedcell>
	<bottleneck>
		As you have upgraded various parts of your crystal network, you have found that there is usually a small handful of constructs acting as the limiting factor in energy transport, either due to their inefficiencies or limitations on their transfer rate. If you could send pulses through the network, almost "ringing" the components, you might be able to identify these bottlenecks.
	</bottleneck>
	<lightgun>
		More than once during your cave expeditions, you have come across great fissures or hollows, and have had nothing but torches with which to (ineffectually) attempt to dispel the cavernous gloom. Sure, you have various constructs which can flood a large area with light, but most are either expensive, slow, or temporary, and at any rate none of those do any good when you venture into new regions without the requisite preparation. What you need is the ability to literally [i]fling[/i] light into the depths.
	</lightgun>
	<endereye>
		You have determined that in a few places in the world lie abandoned structures buried deep underground, and within each lies some sort of gate. Having fashioned some strange-looking items to seek out these structures, you rapidly grew frustrated with their short range and propensity to burst in midair. Undaunted, you have devised an improved version, which is both far more reliable and more powerful, having a far greater range, indestructability, and the ability to return towards you under nearly any circumstance. However, that increased range has led it to occasionally pick up some sort of interference...
	</endereye>
	<spawnerbypass>
		<desc>
			More than once, you have happened upon a location where you were on the other side of a wall from a spawner, and then, while fiddling through your pouch of tools to find the appropriate weaponry, found yourself face-to-face with a mob that appeared on your side of the wall. Never again must that be allowed to happen; once you enter the room and engage the spawner is one thing, but having it activate before you can even see it is neither fair nor enjoyable.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Will not work on spawners which are directly visible
		</notes>
	</spawnerbypass>
	<probe>
		Normally, when you screw up, you can find and fix the mistake simply enough (barring, perhaps, that time your devices melted into gray slag that kills everything that approaches, forcing you to completely abandon the region). However, there have been times where you have stared for hours and not uncovered your error. Clearly you need a tool which can help you in that regard. Naming it, however, has proven difficult; after your original name - involving some mention that it is effectively some sort of probe - was incessantly met with puerile remarks, you have not had ideas on a suitable replacement.
	</probe>
	<telegatelock>
		Teleportation between previsited points, especially if it needs something built at each end, is of little value if you just want to get home from somewhere to which you never plan to return. A wand with a shiny blue sphere helps a bit, but it is expensive to use and there have been times where it has simply not been able to travel particularly far distances. Airing your grievances over that fact to everyone who will listen (and for that matter, even those who will not) might feel rewarding, but does little to solve your dilemma, so you will need another approach, probably building upon things already constructed.
	</telegatelock>
	<widecollector>
		The machinery of your tree farm is a maze of piping and wiring, and every time you want to upgrade or refine it you find drops trapped behind multiple layers of other piping, completely inaccessible unless you feel like tearing a big hole to reach it, and then spending the next 20 minutes figuring out what went where or connects to what. You could apply some sort of magnetisation, but then you collect everything spilled from the farm and your inventory fills with sawdust, charcoal, and apples. What you really need is something which can simply increase your collection range, ideally tuned to specific items.
	</widecollector>
	<enderbucket>
		You have a building full of storage tanks of various liquids, but that does you little good when you need to place a few buckets of lava across your base, 200 blocks away, or find some liquid ender you want to collect while out exploring. Besides the obvious(ly stupid) option of just running back and forth a dozen times, you could just cart drums around with you, but that is still a massive pain, and a lot of the time you find out you need the liquid when already far from the tanks. Something like a bucket which can be innately linked to one or more tanks would be a much more convenient solution.
	</enderbucket>
	<netherkey>
		You have heard stories of a second layer to the nether, filled with several types of structures, many of which contain significant wealth and information and which largely satiate your need for such things. However, something appears to have changed since the stories originated; Much as you may want to do so, you are unable to even access that region, being catapulted backwards when you try (or worse, given what happened that time you tried something rather more outlandish to bypass it). You will need to find another mechanism to nullify this effect.
	</netherkey>
	<recipecache>
		More times than you can count, you have prepared your table for a complicated recipe, filling every stand and using a dozen different item types in a difficult pattern, only to realize that you were missing one of the components. Worse, half the time that item - often being the central item of the recipe - requires the stands to craft [i]it[/i], meaning that you now need to undo all your work so you can prepare to craft that intermediate instead. What you need is something that can collect and remember the recipe pattern, so that you can restore it once you are ready again.
	</recipecache>
	<etherpendant>
		Your recent experiments with luma have proven revealing...in a very literal sense. Something about this fluid allows you to see through the material of reality itself, one use of which is to examine the form and content of cave systems from afar, even the surface (especially of value when searching for buried ruins or oil deposits). However, carting around a bucket of the stuff is annoying to do, even before you consider the inventory space that requires. Given your ability to fashion crystals into wearable versions, you could do that with luma as well, though you obviously cannot just put liquid on a string...right?
	</etherpendant>
	<structmap>
		<desc>
			The artifact you recently found is probably the closest yet you have come to decoding the thoughts of those who built these structures. Perhaps you can pursue that even further, gaining the ability to predict where they might have placed yet other findings.
		</desc>
		<notes>
			Some scans might take some time to complete, and will prevent other scans from being started while in progress
			
			Scans only progress while the map is being viewed, and destroying the map will prevent further scans until the world is refreshed
		</notes>
	</structmap>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
</tools>
