<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tools>
	<wand>
		The manipulator is your first foray into this strange new field of crystal elements and chromatic forces. The tool seems to be your main way of activating blocks, either to start some operation or to change settings on a device. It also seems capable of testing the connectivity of segments of a crystal network, and drawing energy off a pylon into yourself.
	</wand>
	<finder>
		The pylon compass scans the energy field that permeates the world and analyzes it to calculate the location of the nearest pylon of each crystal element. Due to the fact that the energy is always in flux, there is some inaccuracy to the calculation, but the location you are directed to should be within a short walk of the actual pylon.
	</finder>
	<excavator>
		By concentrating elements associated with energy and minerals, you have found that you can apply them to the terrain and excavate a large area. When you release the energy into the ground, it seems to only get conducted along identical materials, but this nonetheless allows you to clear a large area of rock, ores, or other materials with a single stroke.
	</excavator>
	<transition>
		Gray-colored energy seems to have the power to transmute and change, so it is a reasonable guess to think that if applied to the world, with some information of what blocks to place and replace, this power could be used to change large swaths of one block into another, greatly expediting the landscaping process.
	</transition>
	<invlink>
		Mining and other activities tend to fill your inventory with useless junk that seems to accumulate faster than you can get rid of it. By leveraging the power of elements associated with movement, you discover that you can create a linkage between your inventory and one placed somewhere in the world, and one for which you can control the items it transports.
	</invlink>
	<pendant>
		As you have already discovered, crystallized elemental energy can be found scattered around the world, and its proximity imbues the effects of that element on yourself. However, the effect is rather less than convenient to transport in a form that bulky, so a logical next step would be to wear a small part of the crystal to allow you to benefit from its effects at any location.
	</pendant>
	<vacuumgun>
		
	</vacuumgun>
	<lens>
		Crystal Lenses work much like their optical counterparts, focusing, tinting, and otherwise manipulating a beam of energy so that it can apply its effects more strongly over a smaller area.
	</lens>
	<storage>
		Merging small amounts of all the types of crystal yields a crystal that seems to have the ability to store large amounts of energy delivered to it, almost like a battery. This may be convenient for some things that drain this energy yet are too portable for a true crystal network.
	</storage>
	<linktool>
		
	</linktool>
	<warp>
		By experimenting with the darker aspects of another branch of magic, you have suffered some serious consequences, including impaired vision and a nasty tendency for the air around you to come alive with hostile and destructive manifestations of that power. With this mixture, you should be able to keep at least some of those effects at bay.
	</warp>
	<duplicator>
		Building structures that consist of many repeated parts is a tedious task involving less in the way mental vigour and more in the way of running around. Finally, however, you have found a way to scan regions of a structure and allow it to be replicated as many times as you see fit and can afford.
	</duplicator>
	<teleport>
		Long-distance travel has often been a major headache for you, and even with more advanced powers like gliding and flight, you find yourself spending a great deal of time in transit between distant locations. With the mobility wand, you can fling yourself at a distant location, appearing there instantaneously.
	</teleport>
	<builder>
		Building walls and paths is tedious and time-consuming. Fortunately, with the aid of the construction wand, you can extend any continuous surface you like, greatly expediting this process.
	</builder>
</tools>